https://www.appliedrobotics.com/privacy-policy/

Applied Robotics > Privacy Policy
Applied Robotics is dedicated to protecting the privacy of all web visitors. In respect for your privacy Applied Robotics pledges to not share your personal information with any third party. Applied Robotics is a partner of Effecto Group S.p.A. (headquarter in Italy), which has the right to use your personal data and pledges to not share them with any third party. Please read the privacy policy. By using the Applied Robotics website you indicate your acceptance and agreement to the terms of this Privacy Policy.
Privacy Policy
Applied Robotics and Effecto Group are dedicated to protecting the privacy of all web visitors. In respect for your privacy they pledge to not share your personal information with any third party.
Collection Of Information
Applied Robotics and Effecto Group do not collect personal data, (ex.name, address, email) except when voluntarily submitted by website visitors.
For all users
Applied Robotics does not collect any personally identifying data. For  registered seminar attendance the personally identifiable information collected is restricted to the information you provide with your registration for a session. This information is requested when you (a) send an email inquiry; (b) register to receive email updates; (c) place a request for a building site evaluation; or (d) submit an inquiry for a consultation.
The personal data collected may be used if you initiate contact by email and have authorized us to do so. The data may also be accessed if we need to verify your identity to accommodate a request to change or update your account.
Site statistical data which is non-identifiable is used in the aggregate to conduct research to improve the performance and compatibility of the website. This information includes technical data such as browser type, computer platform, as well as click-stream information, searches performed and other website activities which we record and analyze in the aggregate via Google Analytics in an attempt to improve user experience.
Transmission Of Information
When completing a purchase on line, all credit card and billing information transmitted to Applied Robotics website from your browser is encrypted using SSL 2.0 or SSL 3.0. Any communication with a third party for billing or credit card verification will be encrypted with SSL 2.0 or equivalent encryption.
Disclosure Of Information
Applied Robotics will not disclose any personal information you provide with any other party without your permission, except if requested to do so in accordance with a court order, subpoena, or similar legal order, and in the event such disclosure is necessary to protect the rights, property, and safety of Applied Robotics, its users, and other third parties. Applied Robotics will not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. Your data is secure and your confidence in the privacy of your account is very important to us.
Links
Applied Robotics may provide links to third party sites, and web sites may provide links to the Applied Robotics.com web site. Third party web sites operate according to their own terms of use and privacy policies. Applied Robotics has no control over such third party web sites, and therefore you acknowledge and agree that Applied Robotics is not responsible for the availability of such third party sites, and does not endorse and is not responsible or liable for any content, advertising, products, or other materials on or available from such sites. You further acknowledge and agree that Applied Robotics will not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with use of or reliance on any such content, advertising, products, or other materials on or available from such sites. The data provided is quality checked and screened for inappropriate content.
Children
Applied Robotics does not solicit personal information from children. You must be 18 years or older to use this site. This site is not intended for use by children. There will be no content placed on the site by Applied Robotics or display of any third party of a harmful or inappropriate nature. This site is safe for all ages to review the product offerings and informational materials.
Changes To Our Policy
Applied Robotics may amend this policy from time to time. If we make a substantial change in the way Applied Robotics utilizes your personal information, Applied Robotics will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on this page.
Terms of Use
Use of Applied Robotics is subject to the site Terms of Use. By using this web site, Applied Robotics, you are agreeing to be bound by the terms and conditions contained therein.
Contact
If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy, our online practices, or your dealings with this web site, please contact us: info@appliedrobotics.com
Applied Robotics Inc.
